Here we come, friends! You can also touch Big Red in Longbow Canyon.
Now the Treasure Month event has entered the Longbow Canyon map.
But it’s easy to get lost as you go around the underworld points one after another. It doesn't matter,
Dudu didn't sleep at all. Like the nanny, he took everyone to find a spot and collected this video.
The treasure position of the longbow is at home. First of all, point 1 is located on the right side of the harbor pier.
Entering from the outer wall, you will find it under the box on the right.
Point No. 2 is located in the lower left corner of the abandoned village. This location is relatively easy to find, very easy.
It's easy to find. Number 4 is the upper left corner of the small train station, located inside the carriage.
You can find the specific carriage according to the mini map in the video. Number 4 is located in the lower right corner of the station.
After passing the bridge, it is located under the container, which is relatively easy to find.
No. 5 is the outer bridge on the left side of the checkpoint. Go to the station in the middle.
The treasure chest is placed on the platform on the second floor. No. 6 is located on the roadside in the lower right corner of the hotel.
The trunk of the pickup truck can be easily found at the location shown on the mini map.
No. 7 was also in the trunk of the pickup truck, going from the urinal.
Walk up and to the left and you can easily find it when you see the pickup truck. Next is the treasure level upgrade.
It’s also the harder to find treasure chest No. 8 and No. 12. Don’t miss it.
Because it’s really hard to find it yourself! The positional deviation between treasure chest No. 8 and the treasure map is particularly large.
It's located at the top left of the small estate, at the bottom of the tank at the edge of the map. All I can say is,
This location is absolutely disgusting. No. 9 is located on the right side of the Queen's Hotel, towards the one with Mulan Xiang below.
This location is no harder to find than No. 8, even...
The Uluru-style bunker also completely seals the treasure chest.
Hey, I didn’t mean to ask you to knock on the treasure chest after reading it. Number 10 is located in the waterfall below the storage station.
It feels like entering the Shuilian Cave to hunt for treasure. No. 11 is located in the underground passage on the upper left side of the ranch.
It's under a small paper box under the table. Don't miss it when you pass by!
Number 12 is also the last one. It is located on the upper right side of the radar station. Walk forward along the far right side of the radar station.
Behind the black box on the left front. So far,
All twelve Longbow Valley treasure chests have been introduced! To be honest,
I have been looking for No. 8 and No. 9 for I don’t know how long. Please give me a thumbs up.
Pay attention. At the same time, I also roughly designed a treasure hunting route plan.
I took a two-by-three treasure chest and could only hold three treasure maps. My friend, for example, if you storm a radar station,
Then after getting No. 12, you can consider getting No. 10 and No. 4 Treasure Map Station to evacuate.
If you are resurrected on the left side of the map, then numbers 7, 8, and 11 are the obvious choices.
To resurrect friends on the right side of the map, you can consider numbers three, two, and one.
Then make a regular retreat all the way to the left side of the map. As for friends who want to storm the hotel, No.9,
Number six and number five next to the checkpoint.
Without further ado, here is the introduction of the successful treasure map locations in this issue!
Friends who like it, please don’t forget to like and follow. See you in the next issue.